Pride, Prejudice and Mistletoe is a romance, tv
movie film directed by Don McBrearty.
Darcy has always worked hard to prove herself and be successful on her own terms, even
choosing to start her own company, rather than work with her father.
Returning to her hometown for Christmas, Darcy reconnects with an old rival,
restaurant owner Luke, and they are forced to plan a charity event together.
As Darcy spends time with her family and Luke, she starts to realize what matters most in life
and sets out to mend her relationship with her father, and possibly fall in love.
Darcy Fitzwilliam, played by Lacey Chabert.
Luke Bennett, played by Brendan Penny.
Gloria Fitzwilliam, played by Sherry Miller.
Edward Fitzwilliam, played by Art Hindle.
Caylee, played by Anna Hardwick.
Carl Downs, played by Morgan David Jones.
Brendan James Penny (born November 9, 1978) is a Canadian film and
television actor who first became well known to TV audiences as A.J.
Varland in the first season of Whistler that aired in Canada from 2006 to 2008.
He is perhaps best known as Detective Brian Lucas in Motive, a Canadian crime drama centred on a team of Vancouver homicide
detectives, also starring Kristin Lehman, Louis Ferreira and Lauren Holly, which aired from 2013 to 2016.
Brendan currently stars as Kevin O'Brien in the Hallmark Channel family drama
series Chesapeake Shores, which premiered on August 14, 2016.
He has also been the hero of a number of Hallmark originals.
The film explores themes of ex-boyfriend, christmas tree,
restaurant owner, christmas, charity benefit.
The tone is emotional.